

Camia Trefs Sebastian Emanuel

CONTACT

Oncativo 393 Canals - Cordoba Argentina E-mail: canalsdigital@gmail.com

Phone: +5493463645114

OBJECTIVE

At the age of 37, i've decided to pursuit my dream of becoming a professional programmer: something i've been doing as a hobby since i was 13 years old.

I simply and absolutely love it, and now that i am financially stable, i can give myself the chance to make it happen.

The passion i have will definitely push me to do my best to achieve whatever barrier it's been set upon me, through fast learning and consistent dedication towards those goals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Camia Hnos! July 2012 - Present

General Manager

General Manager/Co-Owner of my own Electronics Shop in charge of 3 employees for ten years and counting.

Own Projects

January 2015 - December 2020

Wordpress

Experience in setting up, developing and maintaining Wordpress sites; including:

- Online stores.
- Newspapers.
- Hotel with own booking system for customers.
- PC videogame store with automatic serial code release after successful payment gateway (using Mercado Pago API).
- Online movies website.

Arrimalo

March 2020 - September 2020

Delivery System App

Developed a delivery system app for Google Play such as Uber Eats during the pandemic in 2020:

- Grabbed a code from the Internet and further developed new features (such as whatsapp notification to stores via CallMeBot after a new order arrival, schedulling orders at specific times, adding phone call options, etc).
- Rewrote the entire CSS code to beautify the site.
- Uploaded it to Google Play and made it publicly available.
- Hosted it and made the DB setup in my own server.

Camia Trefs Schastian Fmanuel

Telegram Bot

Coded a Telegram Bot in Python that grabs information from several APIs and presents it to the user.

The bot shows the different dollar prices in Argentina, crypto prices and country risk index (Argentina).

It's been a project that has not taken me more than two weeks but the bot is still running 24/7 in a computer due to the amount of people who was asking me not to take it down.

Bot name in Telegram: @MoraditaDevBot

EDUCATION

Business Administration

March 2004 - July 2008

Universidad de San Andres

 Studies in Business Administration (only lacking the final thesis) at Universidad de San Andres (Buenos Aires, Argentina).

First Certificate in English (FCE)

March 2003 - December 2003

Cambridge University

Also known as B2.

I've also taken an EF SET test with a score of 76/100 (C2 Proficient) level.

Link to the certificate: https://www.efset.org/cert/USqt9c

Web Development

January 2023 - March 2023

CoderHouse.com

Skills learnt during the course:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap 5
- SASS

Full Stack Developer

December 2022 - Present

CoderHouse.com

Currently taking a course of Full Stack Developer at CoderHouse.com

INTERESTS

Playing Chess

Video Games

Football

Programming

Developing Websites

Camia Trefs Sebastian Emanuel 2